Society of Protozoologists records
Society of Protozoologists records
- Series II. Executive Committee, 1947-1995; 439 folders (14.9 linear feet)
  - Subseries II.B. Secretary, 1947-1990; 191 folders (8.25 linear feet)
    - Correspondence/Hutner Award Nominations 1984/12 - 1987/5 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Incorporation Matters 1965/7 - 1986/5 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/Indian Section 1985/6 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence/International Commission 1975/6 - 1977/5 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence/International Relations Committee 1974/6 - 1978/10 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence/International Relations Committee 1980/7 - 1985/9 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence/International Union of Biological Sciences 1967/12 - 1977/1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence/Israeli Section 1963/2 - 1965/11 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence/Israeli Section 1968/3 - 1978/8 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence/Italian Section 1965/12 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence/Italian Section 1977/6 - 1978/2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence/Jahn Fund 1978 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Parasitology 1969/8 - 1972/12 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology 1963/8 - 1964/10 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology 1968/5 - 1973/1 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology 1979/11 - 1980/12 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology 1981/1 - 1982/4 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence/Lee, John 1969/11 - 1973/9 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence/Linnaeus Bicentennial Congress 1955/9 - 1958/7 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence/Mail Out Form Letters 1957/10 - 1962/7 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence/Mail Outs 1967/2 - 1972/6 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence/Manwell, Reginald 1962/9 - 1963/5 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence/Marquardt, William 1968/4 - 1973/12 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Indiana 1958) 1957/10 - 1962/7 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Denver 1961) 1960/10 - 1961/12 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) 1959/9 - 1959/12 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) 1960/1 - 1960/12 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) 1961/1 - 1961/2 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) 1961/3 - 1961/4 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) 1961/5 - 1962/12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Prague 1961) Abstracts 1961/2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Corvallis 1962) 1961/10 - 1962/6 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Amherst 1963) 1962/9 - 1963/7 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Amherst 1963) Executive Committee 1962/11 - 1963/6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Amherst 1963) Forams Symposium 1962/12 - 1963/3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Boulder 1964) 1963/9 - 1964/9 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (London 1965) 1963/10 - 1965/6 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Maryland 1966) 1965/10 - 1966/8 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Leningrad 1967) 1965/11 - 1968/9 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Leningrad 1967) 1968/10 - 1969/9 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Columbus 1968) 1967/10 - 1968/9 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Boston 1969) 1968/1 - 1969/12 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Washington, D.C. 1970) 1967/9 - 1973/2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Meeting ( Ft. Collins 1971) 1970/8 - 1971/8 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Minneapolis 1972) 1972/3 - 1972/8 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Houston 1973) 1973/1 - 1974/1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Middleton 1974) 1974/1 - 1974/8 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Corvallis 1975) 1974/3 - 1975/10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (New York 1975) 1974/11 - 1979/9 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (New Orleans1976) 1975/9 - 1976/5 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Athens, Ga. 1978) 1977/12 - 1978/8 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Washington, D.C. 1980) 1980/3 - 1980/8 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Dallas 1981) 1981/1 - 1981/9 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (San Francisco 1982) 1981/10 - 1982/6 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (New York 1983) 1982/9 - 1983/11 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Athens, Ga. 1984) 1982/6 - 1983/12 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Athens, Ga. 1984) 1984/1-1984/12 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Ohio 1985) Special Executive Committee 1984/1 - 1985/6 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Kenya 1985) 1982/8 - 1985/6 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Rhode Island 1986) 1985/10 - 1986/9 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Illinois 1987) 1986/1 - 1987/6 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence/Meeting (Maryland 1990) 1988/9 - 1990/6 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence/Meeting Sites 1973/7 - 1985/1 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence/Membership Applications 1947 - 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Membership 1980/7 - 1987/10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Membership Committee 1973/10 - 1983/4 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Membership Emeritus 1972/6 - 1979/1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/Membership Honorary 1952/10 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Membership Honorary 1962/5 - 1968/10 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Membership List Requests 1963/4 - 1967/8 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Membership New 1964/6 - 1965/12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/Mexican Section 1979/7 - 1979/9 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence/Muller, Miklos 1982/8 - 1983/10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Noble, Elmer 1969/1 - 1973/7 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Noble, Glenn 1972/2 - 1973/7 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence/Nominating Committee 1954/12 - 1958/4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Nominating Committee 1962/11 - 1963/2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/Nominating Committee 1968/7 - 1980/1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Outka, D. (Treas.) 1970/2 - 1972/12 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/Paulin, J. (Pres.) 1988/10 - 1989/6 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Petherbridge (Griffith Printers) 1962/4 - 1962/9 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Pitelka, D. (Pres.) 1967/1 - 1973/6 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/Publications Cost Committee 1973/2 - 1974/6 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence/duPuytorac (International Committee) 1973/12 - 1974/6 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Samuels, Robert (Treas.) 1959/3 - 1962/12 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/ Samuels, Robert (Treas.) 1963/1 - 1964/12 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/ Samuels, Robert (Treas.) 1965/1 - 1966/6 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence/Samuels, Robert (Pres.) 1968/9 - 1976/10 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence/Scandinavian Section 1967/10 - 1978/6 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence/Schuster, Frederick 1969/9 - 1973/6 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence/Systematics and Evolution Committee 1973/11 - 1978/6 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence/Sleigh, Michael 1987/6 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence/Small, Eugene (Treas.) 1967/11 - 1972/3 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence/Special Publications Committee 1970/1 - 1979/2 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence/ Social Aspects of Science Committee 1957/2 - 1957/6 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence/Soldo, Tony 1974/11 - 1978/3 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence/Tax Exempt Status 1968/6 - 1978/9 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence/Taxonomy Committee 1954/1 - 1957/5 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence/Trager, William 1959/1 - 1962/7 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence/Trager, William 1969/2 - 1973/9 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence/Trager, William 1973/12 - 1977/5 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for London Meeting 1964/4 - 1965/7 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for Leningrad Meeting 1968/2 - 1969/5 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for France Meeting 1972/5 - 1973/10 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for Warsaw Meeting 1981/3 - 1981/5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for Kenya Meeting 1984/8 - 1986/6 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Travel Grants for Japan Meeting 1985/3 - 1989/3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Union of Soviet Socialist Republic 1958/8 - 1960/6 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/University Microfilms International 1985/10 - 1986/10 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Wallace, Franklin (Education Comm.) 1971/4 - 1993/6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Wallace, Franklin (Pres.) 1975/7 - 1978/1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Williams, Norman 1983/7 - 1984/6 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/World Federation of Parasitologists 1962/3 - 1986/6 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence/Zoological Record 1954/4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Computer Print Out 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Expense Report and Statement of Accounts 1968 - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series II.C. Treasurer, 1965-1995; 230 folders (6 linear feet)
    Treasurer files are arranged beginning with general correspondence in date order followed by subject files in alpha order. Correspondence files may also contain information on membership dues payments and award funds. The financial files follow in alpha order. They contain audits, invoices, bank statements and reconciliations, meeting and Journal expenses, tax reports and financial condition statements.
    - Correspondence/ 1965/1 - 1966/10 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/ 1967/1 - 1967/2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/ 1968/1 - 1968/12 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/ 1969/1 - 1969/12 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/ 1970/1 - 1970/6 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/ 1970/7 - 1970/12 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/ 1971/1 - 1972/11 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/ 1973/1 - 1973/6 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence/1973/7 - 1973/12 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/ 1974/1 - 1974/6 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/ 1974/7 - 1974/12 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/ 1975/1 - 1975/6 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence/ 1975/7 - 1975/12 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence/ 1973=6/1 - 1976/12 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence/ 1977/1 - 1977/6 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence/ 1977/7 - 1977/12 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence/ 1978/7 - 1978/12 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence/ 1979/7 - 1979/12 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence/ 1980/7 - 1980/12 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence/ 1981/7 - 1983/12 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence/ 1991/7 - 1991/12 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence/ 1992/7 - 1994/7 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence/ 1994/8 - 1995/2 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence/Accountant 1994/1 - 1994/12 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence/Allen Press 1969/7 - 1981/3 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence/Allen Press 1985/1- 1993/12 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence/Allen Press Contracts 1983/1 - 1996/12 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence/Budget 1989/1 - 1990/12 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence/Business Advisory Committee 1985/11 - 1986/8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence/Business Advisory Committee 1989/5 - 1989/8 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence/Business Committee 1979/1 - 1981/6 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Financial Committee 1991/3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/ Byers, Tom 1982/1 - 1988/10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Byers (Des Moines Savings and Loan) 1973, 1975, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence/Editor (Journal of Protozoology) 1988/6 - 1994/6 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence/Internal Revenue Service 1965/9, 1970/1-1972/12 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology (Back Issues) 1986/8 - 1993/7 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence/Journal of Protozoology (Microform Copies) 1979/2 - 1982/1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Meeting 1984 (Athens, Ga.) 1982/2 - 1984/6 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence/Meeting 1992 (Maryland) 1990/1 - 1991/7 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence/Meeting 1992 (Montana) 1991/9 - 1992/6 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Meeting 1992 (Vancouver) 1991/6 - 1992/11 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/Meeting 1993 (Berlin) 1993/6 ֱ993/8 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/President 1988/1 -1989/6 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/President 1989/7 - 1991/12 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Account (Allen Press) 1973/1 - 1978/12 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Account (Hall) 1980 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Account (Hutner-Jahn Fund) 1982/9, 1982/12 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Account Ledgers 1970 - 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Accounting Statements 1995 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/1 - 1986/2 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/3 - 1986/4 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/5 - 1986/6 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/7 - 1986/8 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/9 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/10 - 1986/11 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1986/12 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1987/1 - 1987/2 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1987/3 - 1987/4 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1989/5 - 1989/6 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1989/7 - 1989/9 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1989/10 - 1989/11 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1989/12 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1990/1 - 1990/2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1990/3 - 1990/4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Accounts Receivables 1990/5 - 1990/6 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Account Recorder 1970 - 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1983/3 - 1983/12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1983/7 - 1983/12 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1984/1 - 1984/6 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1984/7 - 1984/12 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1985/7 - 1985/9 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1985/10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1985/11 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Adjusting Entries 1985/12 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Annual Reports (not complete) 1953 - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Annual Reports 1975 - 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Assets and Fund Balances 1982/6 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Assets and Fund Balances 1982/7 - 1982/12 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Assets and Fund Balances 1983/1 ֱ983/7 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Assets and Fund Balances 1984/3 - 1984/12 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Assets and Fund Balances 1985/3 - 1985/12 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Audit 1986/6 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Audit 1987/6 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Audit 1988/6 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Audit 1991/6 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Audit 1991/7 - 1992/6 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Audit 1992/7 - 1993/6 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Audit 1994/7 - 1995/6 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Audit 1995/7 - 1996/6 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Audit 1996/7 - 1997/6 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1985/6 - 1985/8 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1985/9 - 1985/12 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1986/1 - 1986/3 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1986/4 - 1986/6 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1986/7 - 1986/12 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1987/1 - 1987/6 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1987/7 - 1987/12 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1988/1 - 1988/6 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1988/7 - 1988/12 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1989/1 - 1989/6 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1989/7 - 1989/12 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Balance Sheets 1990/1 - 1990/6 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Bank Books (Capitol Federal) 1991/7 - 1992/12 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1971/7 - 1971/12 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1972/1 - 1972/12 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1973/1 - 1973/7 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1982/7 - 1982/9 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1982/10 - 1982/12 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1983/1 - 1983/6 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1983/7 - 1983/12 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1984/1 - 1984/3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1984/4 - 1984/6 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1984/7 - 1984/9 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1984/10 - 1984/12 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1985/1 - 1985/3 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Bank Deposits and Statements 1985/4 - 1985/6 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Financial/ Bank Statements and Register 1963/1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Capitol Federal) 1979- 1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Coronado Credit Union) 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (DesMoines Savings) 1976 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Douglas County) 1970 ֱ971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Bank Statements(Douglas County) 1973 - 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Douglas County) 1976 - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Douglas County) 1978 - 1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Douglas County) 1980 - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (1st National Bank of Athens) 1981 - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (1st National Bank of Iowa) 1970 - 1972 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (1st National Bank of Tennessee) 1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Peoples Trust New Jersey) 1970 - 1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Bank Statements (Peoples Bank) 1968- 1971 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Budget 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Budget 1987 - 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Check Disbursement Journal 1985/7 - 1986/6 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Check Disbursement and Fund Balances 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Checkbook Ledger (Copies) 1983 - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Checks and Deposits by Month 1984/7 - 1994/6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Checks and Deposits 1994/7 - 1995/6 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Checks and Deposits 1995/7 - 1996/6 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Financial/ Computer Run Balance Sheets 1985/9 - 1986/6 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Financial/ Computer Run Balance Sheets 1986/7 - 1987/7 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Computer Run Balance Sheets 1987/7 - 1988/6 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Financial/ Computer Run Balance Sheets 1988/7 - 1989/6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Financial/ Computer Run Balance Sheets 1989/7 - 1990/6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Deposit 1982/7 - 1983/5 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Deposit 1987/8 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1987/7 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1987/9 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1987/10 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1987/11 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1987/12 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/4 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/5 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/6 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/7 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/8 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/9 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/10 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/11 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1988/12 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/3 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/4 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/5 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Financial/Deposit Reports 1989/6 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Financial/Dividend Statements 1980 ֱ987 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Financial/ Expenses 1970/1 - 1972/6 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1982 - 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1983 - 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1984 - 1985 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1985 - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1986 - 1987 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1987 - 1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Financial/Financial Statements 1988 - 1989 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Financial/General Journal 1978/7 - 1979/6 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Financial/General Journal 1979/7 - 1980/6 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Financial/General Ledger 1971/7 - 1976/6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Financial/General Ledger 1978/7 - 1979/6 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Financial/General Ledger 1980/7 - 1981/6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Financial/General Ledger 1981/7 - 1982/6 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Financial/General Ledger 1983/1 - 1984/6 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Financial/Income Tax Returns 1975, 1978 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) 1969/1 - 1971/12 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) 1972/3 - 1980/6 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) 1982/7 - 1984/5 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) 1984/7 - 1985/4 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) 1986/1 - 1987/12 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Financial/Invoices (Allen Press) Reprints 1969 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Financial/Invoices Business Supplies 1962 - 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Financial/Invoices Griffith Publishing 1966 - 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1983/6 - 1984/6 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1984/7 - 1985/8 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1986/4 - 1987/6 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1987/7 - 1988/12 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1989/1 - 1990/5 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1990/6 - 1990/12 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1991/1 - 1991/12 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1992/1 - 1992/12 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1993/1 - 1993/12 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Financial/Invoices Paid 1994/1 - 1994/6 (Box 16, Folder 20)